# Nathan Smith

Beacon Hill NSW 2100

0402 988 281

nathan.smith1922 @gmail.com

#### SUMMARY

University Student, all-rounder laborer and software developer, with more than 1 year of hypertrophic focused training experience, and extensive experience with different communication reliant jobs. Highly motivated, and eager to delve into new prospective opportunities.

#### EDUCATION -

Balgowlah Boys Campus (Year 12), Graduated 2021

UNSW Sydney (Computer Science/Economics), February 2022 – present

# KEY SKILLS

General Laboring
Heavy Lifting
Barista Experience
Food Service
Coding Development
Commercial Cleaning
Cash Handling

Microsoft Office

#### EXPERIENCE

May 2019 – August 2021
Barista/All Rounder • Tasks including waiting, making coffees, cooking, and cleaning • Ink & Press Café Manly

May 2022 – Jan 2023
General Laborer • Setup and cleanup of events including trade shows and concerts • Show Support

# ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

August 2019

Assistant Software Developer • Internship involving the development of financial technologies in association with banking and cyber security • Razor Risk

July 2022 - Present

Website Developer • Design, setup, and implementation of basic online storefronts for small businesses • Self Employment

# COMMUNICATION

Consistent show of leadership abilities, including project manager for the Balgowlah Boys Coding Club (2020), financial lead and winner of Freshwater business week, cub/scout leader, management overseer for the Balgowlah Boys Coding Club (2021)

Significant experience with customer and client facing jobs

### REFERENCES

[Available upon request.]